guestreservations.com 2018-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Guest Reservations

We value your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information collected from you when you visit the website guestreservations.com (the “Site”), and how Guest Reservations (“Guest Reservations,” “we” or “us”) uses that information. You agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy by visiting the Site.

### Children

Guest Reservations does not seek to collect personal information about children through the Site. If we become aware that a person submitting personal information to us through any part of our Site is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete any information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and deleted the information, then we will of course honor that request.

### Security

We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including monitoring for intrusion attempts, encryption technology, “firewalls,” Secure Socket Layers and security audits and inspections. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. When setting up an account, your information is stored behind a secure server via multiple encryption methods as well as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) on the site. Information stored on the server is only available to a select number of people that have access to these records. The privacy of communication over the Internet cannot be guaranteed because the Internet is not a secure medium. Guest Reservations does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss or damage you my experience or incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the Internet by or to Guest Reservations. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to us through our contact page.

### Information Collected

We collect two kinds of information from visitors to the Site, personal and non personal information. Personal information includes: email address, and physical address, including City and State. Non personal information includes: search preferences, product searches, merchant searches, and general demographics. Our primary purpose in collecting personal and non personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Guest Reservations and our affiliates, or analytics or online customer support provider. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for current and historical search information, authentication and affiliate source. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited or not available.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by emailing us. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes the IP addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/ time stamp, and click stream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We use this information to review trends, to administer our website, to track users’ movements around the web site and to gather demographic information about our customers.

If you have chosen to receive marketing messages from us about our products and services, we may use information from our log files, cookies or pixel tags to help us make those communications more useful to you.

We also get information from your transactions with us, our affiliates or non affiliated third parties such as account activity and your purchase information. We also use information from third parties, including public information, such as verification services and consumer reporting agencies (to comply with regulatory requirements, ensure the accurate data and prevent fraud, for example), or from other sources. We use this information to develop, offer and deliver our products and services, to process transactions in your accounts, and to obey legal and regulatory requirements. We limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum we require to deliver great service to our customers (including telling our customers about our hotel reservation services, deals, and other opportunities through email) and to run our business.

### Use of Information

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to measure interest in the third-party products and services we offer; inform you via email about special offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions of the Site’s use. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple Customer IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use with your permission via the “My Reservations” tab, your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product and services offerings of Guest Reservations or third parties, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By opting in to receive this communication on the “My Reservations” tab of our Web Site, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications under the notification preferences on the “My Reservations” tab of our Web Site. You may make changes to your notification preferences on the “My Reservations” tab at any time or you may contact a customer service representative through our contact page. We reserve the right to send you specific administrative notices that are required by law, regulation or as needed to service your account.

We may use your personal information to send marketing emails to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional email communications, you may opt out of receiving them by going to your “My Reservations” tab or by emailing us through our contact page or by calling Customer Service at (866) 238-4218.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We share your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us through our contact page. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide you with the ability to order the third-party products and services offered through the Site.

_Advertisers_. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address and password are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent.

We collect booking information via our forms that include the collection of personal and financial information. Some of these transaction pages may not appear on guestreservations.com pages and we do not control the privacy of the information given on these pages. Once the user submits the info, payment is made and verified, the booking is confirmed and removed from our inventory and passed on to the third party vendor booking the travel. The booking info then gets passed along to the third party for fulfillment. We do collect payment and verify credit card info to complete the booking, but we act only as the booking agent. The third party will receive the confirmation request from the guest for the reservation and then their privacy policy would be in effect. We do not have any control over the third party use of information or their privacy policies. Guest Reservations is disclosing this information to users so that they have the option to not do business on the Site. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to book with such lodging establishments. We may occasionally share information with our service providers that is in aggregate form. This information does not contain any personal information as it is in aggregate form and used to develop products that may be of interest to our customers. We may from time to time contract with third parties to handle surveys on the site. Upon completion of these projects, all information is returned to us. These companies that act as our service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

_Legal Requests_. Guest Reservations cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and our other customers from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address and Customer ID history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or report suspected illegal activity. If Guestreservations.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us through our contact page.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Other Websites

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. This Site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that Guest Reservations is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy policy of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are third-party providers of products or services, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Guest Reservations does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy when you visit the Site to review the current policy. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. Guest Reservations will use the information collected on the Site in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact Customer Service through our contact page or call Customer Service at (866) 238-4218. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact us.

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 16, 2017.**
